(Leonard:)Hey, look at this.
"Dear Roger, to be opened
upon your first great discovery.
Love, Mom."
(Leonard:)Wow, look at the date.
He saved this 50 years
and never got to open it.
(Howard:)That's intense.
(Raj:)Poor Roger Abbott.
(laughing): Roger Abbott sounds
just like Roger Rabbit.
(Raj:)Roger Abbott, Roger Abbott,
Roger Abbott.
(Raj:)Oh, my God, Leonard, I know
he's dead, but try it. It's fun!
(Raj:)Roger Abbott,
Roger Abbott...
DAN:
Penny!
(chuckles)
Oh, my rookie of the year.
(Penny:)Oh, Dan. My boss who didn't want
to hire me
(Penny:)and now's a little hug machine.
(chuckles)
Oh,
(Dan:)look at you. Brand-new
(Dan:)and already
the third best sales rep.
Aw. Yes.
Why don't you come over
to my table.
(Penny:)I'll be right there.
Bernadette's just
parking the car.
(Dan:)Oh, good.
(Dan:)Bernadette. Cute, sweet...